Guide to the George P. Garrett Papers, 1929-2008 (bulk 1960-2000)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings Series, 1957-1996 and undated
  - Writings by Others Subseries, ca. 1970-1994 and undated
    - Settle, Mary Lee, Review of Henry Carlisle's Voyage to the 1st of Dec. (Box WO 14)
    - Settle, Mary Lee, Paragraph 11 (Box WO 14)
    - Settle, Mary Lee, The Days of October (Box WO 14)
    - Seward, William, F. Scott Fitzgerald's Associations... (Box WO 14)
    - Sharp, Rhod, Solo (Box WO 14)
    - Shawn, Richard, The Sleeper (Box WO 14)
    - Shaya, Greg, Travels in Nihilon (Box WO 14)
    - Sheldon, Tim, Poems (Box WO 14)
    - Simmons, Edgar, Poems (Box WO 14)
    - Simmons, J. Edgar, Motivation: the Moral Eroticism and The Green Key (Box WO 14)
    - Simms, L.L., Poems (Box WO 14)
    - Simon, Rose, Poems (Box WO 14)
    - Singer, Ron, Spots (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Da Ponte (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Sorrows of Fat City: Bloom and the Decline of Civility (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Translations of hymns of Prudentius (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Poems (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Luke's Book (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Translation of Seneca's Medea (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, The Cliff (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, The Year in the Short Story, 1986-1994, (5 folders) (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Translation of The Fables of Avianus (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Translation of Duessa (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Translations of epigrams of John Owens (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Dreams, Ideals, and Jokes (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Translation of Ovid's Ibis (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Rounding the Horn and other poems (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, History, Fate, and Freedom: A Look at George Garrett's New Novel (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, King Saul (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Collected Poems (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Basic Training (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Short Stories Are Not Real Life, (2 folders) (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Publish and Perish (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Coming Out Every Week (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Get Thee to a Nunnery: Two Shakespearean Metafictions (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Translation of Thyestes (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Duessa's Version (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, 'The Succession': George Garrett's Book for All Seasons (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Name Six Famous Belgians (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Ovid in Exile (Box WO 14)
    - Slavitt, David, Review of Richard Burgin's Man Without Memory and David Huddle's The High Spirits (Box WO 14)
    - Sloan, James Park, A Small War (Box WO 14)
    - Smith, Keith, Life Sentences (Box WO 15)
    - Smith, R.B., Stay Close to Your Desks and Never Go to Sea (Box WO 15)
    - Smith, William Jay, Poems (Box WO 15)
    - Snow, Wilbert, Poems (Box WO 15)
    - Soderfelt, Eloise, Poems (Box WO 15)
    - Sokolov, Raymond, Who Should Pay the Piper for Piss Christ? (Box WO 15)
    - Solomon, Andy, Review of The Writer's Chapbook (Box WO 15)
    - Sonde, Susan, The Saved (Box WO 15)
    - Sopko, John, The Robbery and Beyond the High Grass (Box WO 15)
    - Sorrells, Robert, The Blacktop Champion of Ickey Honey and other stories (Box WO 15)
    - Spears, Monroe K. and Wier, Allen, Reviews of Entered from the Sun, (2 folders) (Box WO 15)
    - Spelvin, George, Fragments from the Notebooks... (Box WO 15)
    - Spyker, John H., A One Night Stand-In (Box WO 15)
    - Standiford, Les, Miscellaneous papers (Box WO 15)
    - Standiford, Les, Deal, (2 folders) (Box WO 15)
    - Stanford, Frank, Poems, (2 folders) (Box WO 15)
    - Stanton, Maura, Nijinsky, John McCormack, and Cries of Swimmers (Box WO 15)
    - Steinke, Darcey, My Father's Girlfriends and On This Bare Island (Box WO 15)
    - Steinke, Darcey, Obedience (Box WO 15)
    - Steinke, Jonathan Paul, Un Sejour dans la Nuit (Box WO 15)
    - Stern, Horst, The Last Hunt (Box WO 15)
    - Stevens, Mariflo, Some Say Tomato (Box WO 15)
    - Stevenson, John, Reflections from a Retired Position (Box WO 15)
    - Still, Mary, Chapters 1 & 2 from an unfinished novel (Box WO 15)
    - Stillwell, Sgt. Harry E., World on Fire (Box WO 15)
    - Stokesbury, Leon, Often in Different Landscapes (Box WO 15)
    - Sullivan, Chester, The Mountain Quail (Box WO 15)
    - Sullivan, Walter, Afterwords (Box WO 15)
    - Sullivan, Walter, Fiction in a Dry Season: Some Signs of Hope (Box WO 15)
    - Sullivan, Walter, The Recovery of Literature (Box WO 15)
    - Taylor, F.H. Griffin, A Point in Time, A Place in Space (Box WO 15)
    - Taylor, Henry, A Road Sufficient for the Purpose (Box WO 15)
    - Taylor, Henry, Good-bye to the Goya Girl (Box WO 15)
    - Taylor, Henry, After a Movie and How to Enjoy a Film Festival (Box WO 15)
    - Taylor, Peter, Their Losses and Two Pilgrims (Box WO 15)
    - Teto, Randeane, Merle's and Marilyn's Mink Ranch (Box WO 15)
    - Theroux, Alexander, Poems (Box WO 15)
    - Theroux, Alexander, Christmas Eve at the Gordon Crumms (Box WO 15)
    - Theroux, Alexander, The Confessions of Mrs. Motherwell (Box WO 15)
    - Thompson, Bill, The Journey of the Fisher King, (2 folders) (Box WO 15)
    - Thompson, Bill, Excerpt from Journey of the Fisher King (Box WO 15)
    - Thompson, Burn, Poems (Box WO 15)
    - Threthewey, Eric, Evening Knowledge (Box WO 15)
    - Tillinghast, Richard, Our Flag Was Still There, (2 folders) (Box WO 15)
    - Tillinghast, Richard, 15 poems by Richard Tillinghast (Box WO 15)
    - Tilghman, Christopher, The Long Way Around (Box WO 15)
    - Topp, Bob, The Horns of the Ram (Box WO 15)
    - Torstenson, Ann, Poems (Box WO 15)
    - Trainer, Mark, Biography of Peter Taylor (Box WO 15)
    - Trotti, Lamar, The Ox-Bow Incident (Box WO 16)
    - Truesdale, C.W., Moon Shots (Box WO 16)
    - Turneau, Ted, Poems (Box WO 16)
    - Tuttleton, James W., The Tension Between Emerson and Hawthorne (Box WO 16)
    - Vance, Jane Gentry, Review of Garrett's Understanding Mary Lee Settle (Box WO 16)
    - Vella, Augusta Evalee, Son (Box WO 16)
    - Waldan, Roy, Story (Box WO 16)
    - Walker, David, Poems (Box WO 16)
    - Walker, David, Moving Out: poems 1962-69 (Box WO 16)
    - Wall, Eamonn, Review of Tom McGonigle's Going to Patchoque (Box WO 16)
    - Wallace, Connie, Hillary Highheels (Box WO 16)
    - Walters, Neal Lawrence, In Barefoot Country (Box WO 16)
    - Walton, Jackie, Budapest Series, Part 1 (Box WO 16)
    - Walton, Jackie, The Pretense of Air, (2 folders) (Box WO 16)
    - Walton, Jackie, The Third Floor (Box WO 16)
    - Walton, Jackie, Untitled (Box WO 16)
    - Walton, Jacqueline, Blood from a Stone (Box WO 16)
    - Walton, Kathy, Daddy (Box WO 16)
    - Warner, William, Poems (Box WO 16)
    - Warren, Barbara, Who Kissed the Corpse?, (2 folders) (Box WO 16)
    - Weiseman, Jack, Poems (Box WO 16)
    - Weismiller, E.R., Poems (Box WO 16)
    - Weissberg, Melissa, Flight Patterns (Box WO 16)
    - Weissberg, Melissa, No Haven (Box WO 16)
    - West, Woody, A Graduation Address for '92. (Box WO 16)
    - Whalen, Tom, The Ride (Box WO 16)
    - Whalen, Tom, Chozen at 4 am (Box WO 16)
    - Whalen, Tom, My Only Homerun (Box WO 16)
    - Whalen, Tom, Film Noir: Killer Style (Box WO 16)
    - Whalen, Tom, Professors (Box WO 16)
    - Whalen, Tom, The Reader becomes Text Methods of Experimentation in Garrett's 'Elizabeth and James' (Box WO 16)
    - Whalen, Tom, Head in a Box (Box WO 16)
    - White, Lourine, Echo From a Sheltered Valley (Box WO 16)
    - Whitehall, John, Review of Louis Rubin's An Apple for My Teacher (Box WO 16)
    - Wier, Allen, Writing as an Act of Faith (Box WO 16)
    - Wier, Allen, Ghosts Made Flesh, review of Garrett's Entered From the Sun (Box WO 16)
    - Wilbur, Ellen, Short stories (Box WO 16)
    - Wilbur, Ellen, Winds and Birds and Human Voices, (2 folders) (Box WO 16)
    - Wilbur, Ellen, At the V.A. Hospital (Box WO 16)
    - Wilbur, Ellen, The History Teacher (Box WO 16)
    - Wilken, Robert, The Christian Intellectual Tradition (Box WO 16)
    - Williams, Miller, Poems (Box WO 16)
    - Willingham, Calder, How to Write Novels and Screenplays (Box WO 16)
    - Wilson, Clyde, Should the South Survive? (Box WO 16)
    - Wilson, Clyde, Review of Garrett's Understanding Mary Lee Settle (Box WO 16)
    - Wingate, Jane, Going on the Roof (Box WO 16)
    - Winehap, Bob, Juan (Box WO 16)
    - Wise, Hope, A Rich Widow (Box WO 16)
    - Wise, Hope, Annie's Story and poems (Box WO 16)
    - Wister, Fanny Kemble, Owen Wister' Out West: His Journals and Letters (Box WO 16)
    - Woelfel, Sal, The Duckling Essays (Box WO 16)
    - Woiwode, Larry, Television: the Cyclops that Eats Books (Box WO 16)
    - Wolfe, Gregory, Novels as History: the Art of Andrew Lytle (Box WO 16)
    - Wood, George R., Notes on Attempted Sanity (Box WO 16)
    - Wright, Stephen, Of Death, No News (Box WO 16)
    - Wright, Stuart, George Garrett: A Bibliographic Chronicle (Box WO 16)
    - Yates, James, Confusions on Entrances to a Bird House (Box WO 16)
    - Yates, James, Innocent Bystanders (Box WO 16)
    - Yount, John, Toots in Solitude, (2 folders) (Box WO 16)
    - Yount, John, Hardcastle, (2 folders) (Box WO 16)
- Correspondence Series, 1929-1995 and undated
  The correspondence series is divided into five subseries: the Chronological Correspondence Subseries, and Alphabetical Correspondence Subseries A, B, C, and D.
  - Chronological Correspondence Subseries, 1929-1995 and undated (bulk 1940-1995)
    Contains letters from students, colleagues, friends, literary figures, and family members concerning literary, academic, and personal matters. Arranged chronologically by year. Box 1 contains material pertaining to Garrett's childhood and early education and is arranged in a separate run in chronological order.
    - 1929-1941, (2 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 1)
    - 1941-1943, (2 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 1)
    - 1941-1943, (2 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 1)
    - 1941-1944, (3 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 1)
    - 1942-1946: Sewanee Military Academy, (2 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 1)
    - 1946-1947: Princeton Correspondence, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 1)
    - 1947: Camp Mt. Mitchell, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 1)
    - 1947: The Hill School, (2 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 1)
    - 1940-1952: Personal, (2 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 1)
    - 1940, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1941, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1945, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1947, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1948, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1949, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1950, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1951, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1955, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1957, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1958, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1959, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1960, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1961, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1961 Oct. 11-1964 Dec. 4, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1962, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1963, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1964, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1965, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1965 Jan. 10-1968 Jun. 16, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1966, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1967, (2 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1968, (4 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1969, (2 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1970, (1-3 of 11 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 2)
    - 1970, (4-11 of 11 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 3)
    - 1971, (3 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 3)
    - 1972, (3 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 3)
    - 1973, (2 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 3)
    - 1974, (2 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 3)
    - 1975, (2 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 3)
    - 1976, (1 folder) (Box Chron. Corr. 3)
    - 1977, (2 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 3)
    - 1978, (2 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 4)
    - 1979, (2 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 4)
    - 1980, (2 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 4)
    - 1981, (3 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 4)
    - 1982, (4 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 4)
    - 1983, (12 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 4)
    - 1984 (1-2 of 17 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 4)
    - 1984 (3-17 of 17 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 5)
    - 1985 (1-7 of 11 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 5)
    - 1985 (8-11 of 11 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 6)
    - 1986, (10 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 6)
    - 1987 (1-5 of 17 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 6)
    - 1987 (6-17 of 17 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 7)
    - 1988 (1-5 of 28 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 7)
    - 1988 (6-22 of 28 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 8)
    - 1988 (23-28 of 28 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 9)
    - 1989 (1-12 of 27 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 9)
    - 1989 (13-27 of 27 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 10)
    - 1990 (1-19 of 29 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 11)
    - 1990 (20-29 of 29 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 12)
    - 1991 (1-7 of 23 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 12)
    - 1991 (8-19 of 23 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 13)
    - 1991 (20-23 of 23 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 14)
    - 1992 (1-12 of 24 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 14)
    - 1992 (13-24 of 24 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 15)
    - 1993 (1-4 of 20 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 15)
    - 1993 (5-20 of 20 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 16)
    - 1994 (1-12 of 14 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 17)
    - 1994 (13-14 of 14 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 18)
    - 1995, (6 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 18)
    - N.d., (21 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 19)
    - N.d., (15 folders) (Box Chron. Corr. 20)
  - Alphabetical Correspondence Subseries: Group A, ca. 1961-1995 and undated
    Contains letters from students, colleagues, friends, literary figures, and family members concerning literary, academic, and personal matters. Arranged alphabetically by the last name of the correspondent. All items from each correspondent are contained within one folder unless otherwise indicated.
    - Aaron, Howard (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Abbot, Louise (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Abdou, Elias (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Abse, Dannie (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Ackerman, Diane (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Addison, Lee (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Ager, Verkuilen (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Akerman, Hugh (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Akerman, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Albright, William (Bill) (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Albritton, A. Dallas (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Aldershof, Mrs. Kent (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Allen, Bruce (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Allen, Eloise (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Allen, John A. (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Allen, Mrs.R (Frani) (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Anderson, Leif (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Anderson, Emily Draper (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Antrim, Don (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Antrim, Harry (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Appleman, Philip (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Ardizzone, Tony (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Armstrong, Robert G. (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Arnold, Judd (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Ashbery, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Ashley, Franklin (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Atkins, Mary Ellen (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Atkins, Tom (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Atkins, Thomas (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Atkinson, Clinton J. (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Aycock, Wendell (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - A (Misc.) (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Babcock, Bert (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bagg, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bain, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Baird, Ida (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Baird, Max (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Baker, Carlos (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bale, Joy (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Ball, Donald (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Barnstone, H. (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Barnstone, Willis (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Barrett, James Lee (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Barrett, Marvin (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Barriom Raymond (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Barrol, J. Leeds (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Barry, Richard A. (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Barth, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Battestin, Martin and Ruth (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Baumbach (see Bumas) (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Baumbach, Jonathan (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bausch, Richard (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bayle, Joy (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Beachman, Walton (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Beattie, Ann (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Beck, Virginia L. (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Beebe, Anne (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bell, Charles G. (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bell, Madison (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bell, Marvin (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Belitt, Ben (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Benedetti, Robert L. (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Benedict, Pinckney (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Berlind, Bruce (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bernhard, Ruth (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bernstein, Jane (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Berry, D. C. (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Berry, Jason (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Berto, Giuseppe (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bertolino, James (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Berryhill, Michael (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Betts, Doris (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Blotner, Joseph (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Biddle, Katherine (Mrs. Francis) (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Biquenet, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bitker, Marjorie (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bjornson, Richard (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Blackburn, William (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Blackmur, R.P. (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Blotner, J.L. (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Boatwright, James (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bode, Carl (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bogan, Louise (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bonazzi, Bob (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Booth, Jay (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Borden, Ed. B. (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bornhauser, Fred (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bourjaily, Vance (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bowers, Fredson (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Boyle, Kay (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bracker, Jon (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bradley, Jerry ( The New Mexico Humanities Review) (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Briggs, Curtisy (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Brinni, John Maliom (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Brock, Van (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Brookes, Jacqueline (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Brooks, Cleanth (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Brooks, Roger (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Broughton, Irv (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Brower, Brock (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Brown, Gwyneth (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Brown, Jerry (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Brown, Pryde (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Brown, Vaughan (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bruccoli, Matthew (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Buechner, Frederick (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bumas, Jonathan (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Burkert, Claire (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Burroughs, Edgar Rice (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Bush, G. F. (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Byron, Stuart (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - B (Misc.) (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Cacciatore, Edoardo (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Caetani, Princess (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Cain, Gloria (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Cajina-Vega, Mario (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Campbell, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Campo, Cristina (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Cane, Priscilla (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Caples, Minerva (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Cardwell, Harry (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Carr, Barnes (Box Alpha. Corr. A1)
    - Carr, John, (5 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Carringer, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Carter, Virginia (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Case, William (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Cassill, Kay (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Cassill, R. V. (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Chappell, Fred (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Chappell, Patsy (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Chenoweth, H. Avery (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Cherry, Kelly (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Cheuse, Alan (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Cheever, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Chilton, W. E. (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Christ, Ronald (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Chute, Carolyn (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Ciardi, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Clark, David R. (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Clark, Geoff (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Clemmons, Walter (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Clift, Gary (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Cogshell, Rosanne (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Cohen, Marc (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Cohen, Sarah B. (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Coindreau, Maurice (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Coleman, M. M. (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Collin, Francis (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Collmer, Robert G. (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Colony, Joyce (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Colum, Padrick (Padraic?) (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Colvert, Jim (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Commins, Dorothy (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Conner, Jack E. (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Cook, Thomas (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Cooley, Peter (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Copper, Harriet (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Core, George (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Corn, Charles (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Corrigan, Robert W. (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Corrington, John William (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Corrington, William (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Cousin, Herbert (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Cowen, Walker (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Cowley, Malcolm (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Cox, Nana (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Cox, Steve (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Coxe, Louis O. (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Creagh, John P. (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Creeger, George (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Crepeau, Marcel G. (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Crow, Edith (Baker) (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Currier, John (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - C (Misc.) (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Dahl, Roald (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Danielson, Patricia, (3 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A2)
    - Danielson, Patricia, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Daniell, Rosemary (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Darr, Ann, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Davis, Paxton (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Davis, L.J. (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Day, Douglas (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Day, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Degener, Claire (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - DeJong, David C. (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Delbanco, Nicholas (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Den Boer, James (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Denham, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Denny, Dave (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Denny, Reuel (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Denton, Mrs. Walter (Virginia) (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dern, Susan (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dew, Joan (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Deutsche, Babette (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Diamond, I. A. L. (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dick, Donna (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dickey, James (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dickey, R. P. (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dickey, Larry (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dike, Donald (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dillard, Annie (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dillard, Richard, (2 folders) (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dinsmore, Brad (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dipiero, Simione (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Di Piero, W. S. (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Doar, Harriet (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dodrill, Davan (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Domroe, Elissa (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Donadio, Candida (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dorris, George (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dow, Paul E. (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dowden, Will (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Downer, Alan (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Downs, Robert C.S. (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Drinkwater, Harry (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dunlap, Bernie (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dunn, Alice and Evans (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dunning, Steve (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Durbin, Reed (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dutcher, Lavalle Simms (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Duvall, Severn (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Dabney -- Dzul (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Early, Benjamin (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Early, Robert (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - East, Charles (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)
    - Eastlake, William (Box Alpha. Corr. A3)